<NomaiObject xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/xen-42/outer-wilds-new-horizons/main/NewHorizons/Schemas/text_schema.xsd">

	<!--Main NomaiText.Branch-->
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>1</ID>
		<Text>
			ORYZA: Hello students! As I mentioned in class the other day, our clan is hoping for you all to take part in our entry for the upcoming festival. So, welcome to our entry!
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>2</ID>
		<ParentID>1</ParentID>
		<Text>
			ORYZA: We've decided to focus on education for this festival, which is where you all are going to come in! This entire star system is actually an educational device made to help students like yourselves understand how such a system works.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>3</ID>
		<ParentID>2</ParentID>
		<Text>
			ORYZA: As you can see below you, a number of different planets have been created for you to work with. You are free to build on and reshape these planets as you see fit, in order to create a system that demonstrates your understanding. Think of yourself as... architects!
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>4</ID>
		<ParentID>3</ParentID>
		<Text>
			ORYZA: At the center of this platform is the orrery, a vital tool in your shaping of this system. While an orrery is normally a miniature representation of a star system, it is more accurate in this case to say that the star system is a scaled-up representation of the orrery!
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>5</ID>
		<ParentID>4</ParentID>
		<Text>
      ORYZA: That may be a bit confusing, but I'll leave it to you all to discover what I mean by that! To make navigation easier in this system, we've placed warp transmitters on each planet (mostly on the north pole) that will bring you to and from this station.
    </Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>6</ID>
		<ParentID>5</ParentID>
		<Text>
			ORYZA: You will have finite resources for this project, so make sure to use them with care. Other than that, have fun! You will all be given approximately two weeks to complete your project before it is submitted to the festival, so just make sure to have everything done by then.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>7</ID>
		<ParentID>6</ParentID>
		<Text>
			ORYZA: Oh, and one last thing. Since this is meant to demonstrate your understanding of star systems, I'll need you to tell me six different requirements that your system will meet to be similar to a real star system. This is a <![CDATA[<i>graded</i>]]> project after all. Have fun little ones!
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<!--Ship log reveals go here-->
</NomaiObject>
