<AstroObjectEntry xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
                 xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/Outer-Wilds-New-Horizons/new-horizons/main/NewHorizons/Schemas/shiplog_schema.xsd">
	<ID>Walker_Jam5_Station</ID>

	<Entry>
		<ID>Walker_Jam5_Station_ProjectRequirements</ID>
		<Name>Project Requirements</Name>
		<Curiosity>Walker_Jam5_Station_ProjectRequirements</Curiosity>
		<IsCuriosity/>

		<ExploreFact>
			<ID>Walker_Jam5_Station_ProjectRequirements_Count</ID>
			<Text>A set of Nomai students were assigned a project to prepare this star system to be their clan's entry in a festival. They had to propose 6 requirements that the system would fulfill in order to demonstrate their understanding of the mechanisms of natural star systems.</Text>
		</ExploreFact>

		<ExploreFact>
			<ID>Walker_Jam5_Station_ProjectRequirements_OppositeSides</ID>
			<Text>Any two planets that share an orbit must be on opposite sides of the sun.</Text>
		</ExploreFact>

		<ExploreFact>
			<ID>Walker_Jam5_Station_ProjectRequirements_DoubleSand</ID>
			<Text>Multiple planets in the system must have sand.</Text>
		</ExploreFact>

		<ExploreFact>
			<ID>Walker_Jam5_Station_ProjectRequirements_DriedSeabed</ID>
			<Text>The system must contain an exposed dried seabed.</Text>
		</ExploreFact>

		<ExploreFact>
			<ID>Walker_Jam5_Station_ProjectRequirements_FrozenPlanet</ID>
			<Text>Solid ice must be present on a planet in the system. The system's star is too hot to allow ice to re-freeze even in the furthest orbit. A Nomai named Adonsonia proposed somehow blocking the star's heat from reaching the planet they want to freeze.</Text>
		</ExploreFact>

		<ExploreFact>
			<ID>Walker_Jam5_Station_ProjectRequirements_WarpAlignment</ID>
			<Text>The warp transmitter must be aligned with at least one receiver.</Text>
		</ExploreFact>

		<ExploreFact>
			<ID>Walker_Jam5_Station_ProjectRequirements_FinalLocation</ID>
			<Text>Once all 5 requirements are met, the project must be submitted in the core of "Glacial Abyss!". A Nomai named Alnus pointed out that it is impossible to reach the core using quantum entanglement while all the other project requirements are met.</Text>
		</ExploreFact>
	</Entry>

	<Entry>
		<ID>Walker_Jam5_Station_Orrery</ID>
		<Name>Orrery Station</Name>
		<Curiosity>Walker_Jam5_Station_ProjectRequirements</Curiosity>

		<ExploreFact>
			<ID>Walker_Jam5_Station_Orrery_Fact</ID>
			<Text>The station contains an orrery of the system. A Nomai named Oryza claims the system is a scaled-up representation of the orrery.</Text>
		</ExploreFact>
		
		<ExploreFact>
			<ID>Walker_Jam5_Station_Orrery_Warp</ID>
			<Text>There are warp transmitters connected to the station on the north pole of most planets in the system.</Text>
		</ExploreFact>
	</Entry>

</AstroObjectEntry>